collabera.com 2018-07-11

# Collabera | Privacy Policy

Your access to and use of this site is subject to the following terms and conditions and all applicable laws. By accessing and using this site, you accept the following terms and conditions, without limitation or qualification.

This website is administered by Collabera Inc. The primary purpose of collabera.com is to be a dynamic resource and business tool to assist you in understanding Collabera offerings and matching your needs and requirements with Collabera offerings. It is also utilized as a portal for current and future employees to provide, and access, information in a secure and controlled way. We want you to feel secure when visiting our site and are committed to maintaining your privacy when doing so.

Why do we gather information?: (1) to assess the sites effectiveness and usefulness to those who enter the site and search it contents; (2) to allow for application to positions posted on the site; and (3) to allow electronic submission of required paperwork.

One example of information we collect indirectly is through our Internet access logs. When you access collabera.com, your Internet address is automatically collected and is placed in our Internet access logs.

As a global organization, data we collect may be transferred internationally throughout Collabera's worldwide organization. We will not sell individual information and will share it only with our subsidiaries and required service providers and clients where it is applicable and consent has been provide by you for such use. If Collabera requires sensitive personal data from you then Collabera will specifically ask for your consent to our proposed uses of the data. The references to "sensitive personal data" are to the various categories of personal data identified by the United States of America and other data privacy laws, including other country's laws and policies, as requiring special treatment, including in some circumstances the need to obtain explicit consent. These categories may include but are not limited to personal identity numbers, personal data about personality and private life, racial or ethnic origin, nationality, membership of a trade union or profession or trade association, physical or mental health, addictions, property matters or criminal record (including information about suspected criminal activities).

We take appropriate steps to maintain the security of your data on collabera.com. However you should understand that the open nature of the Internet is such that data may flow over networks without security measures and may be accessed and used by people other than those for whom the data is intended.

It is completely up to you whether or not you want to access and use this site and provide the information requested if applicable.
